Guide to the Newport Restoration Foundation Records, 1968-1999 (bulk 1968-1982) RL.01440
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Newport Restoration Foundation records
1968-1999 (bulk 1968-1982)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Newport Restoration Foundation
RL.01440
23.8 Linear Feet
In 1968, Doris Duke established the Newport Restoration Foundation (NRF) with the express purpose of preserving, interpreting, and maintaining landscape and objects reflecting the 18th- and 19th-century architectural culture of Aquidneck Island (Newport, R.I.). In creating the foundation, Doris Duke had a simple plan: to purchase dilapidated 18th century homes and meticulously restore them so that every detail was as historically accurate as possible. During the next three decades, preservation remained a major focus among her many charitable endeavors. Saving eighty-three properties was an undertaking on a scale and scope that has never been repeated. Doris Duke gave $21.9 million to the Newport Restoration Foundation, the largest philanthropic gift she made to a single organization during her lifetime. The collection documents the daily business activities of the Newport Restoration Foundation (NRF), including purchases, renovations, and renting of various NRF homes, photo inventories of the furniture and other household items at each restored NRF home, weekly progress reports, and other routine matters. The architectural records in this collection are related to the renovation of several of the NRF homes. The materials in this collection are arranged chronologically and alphabetically thereunder.
14,050 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use. Due to the fragility of the Architectural records, The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Newport Restoration Foundation Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a donation from the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation in June 2009.
Historical Note
In the 1950s, Doris Duke once again became a frequent visitor to Newport, R.I. A growing awareness and concern for the state of Newport’s historic architecture led her to establish the Newport Restoration Foundation (NRF) in 1968. The non-profit institution was formed with the express purpose of preserving, interpreting, and maintaining landscape and objects reflecting the 18th- and 19th- century architectural culture of Aquidneck Island (Newport, R.I.). In creating the foundation, Doris Duke had a simple plan: to purchase dilapidated 18th century homes and meticulously restore them so that every detail was as historically accurate as possible. After the houses were restored, the NRF maintained the houses and rented them as private living spaces. This model of "living preservation" was groundbreaking in the field of historic preservation. During the next three decades, preservation remained a major focus among her many charitable endeavors. Saving eighty-three properties was an undertaking on a scale and scope that has never been repeated. Doris Duke gave $21.9 million to the Newport Restoration Foundation, the largest philanthropic gift she made to a single organization during her lifetime.
Collection Overview
The Newport Restoration Foundation Records (formerly NRF.12) are part of the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation Historical Archives which were donated to the Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library by the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation. The collection spans the years 1968 to 1999, although a bulk of the material dates from 1968 to 1982. While the collection is arranged into three series: Adminstrative Records, Financial Records, and Architectural Records, the majority of materials are financial records associated with the daily operations and management of the foundation and its assets. Overall, the collection documents the daily business activities of the Newport Restoration Foundation (NRF), including purchases, renovations, and renting of various NRF homes, photo inventories of the furniture and other household items at each restored NRF home, weekly progress reports, and other routine matters. The architectural records in this collection are related to the renovation of several of the NRF homes. The materials in this collection are arranged chronologically and alphabetically thereunder.
Related Material
Doris Duke Papers on the Rough Point Residence, 1922-1997
Duke University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Architecture -- Designs and plans; Newport (R.I.); Architectural drawing -- United States -- 20th century; Architecture -- Conservation and restoration; Duke, Doris; Newport Restoration Foundation; Newport Restoration Foundation
- Administrative Records, 1968-1999
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains a variety of materials related to the business activities of the Newport Restoration Foundation. Materials included are correspondence and memoranda regarding the purchase, renovation, and renting of NRF homes in Newport, R.I., statements of receipts and disbursements for NRF, newspaper clippings regarding the activities of and awards to the NRF, reports and summaries, weekly progress reports for work performed at various NRF homes, photo inventories (including color photographs) of furniture and other household items at each restored NRF home, NRF business plans and other various NRF business activities. Also includes correspondence regarding the writing of an article about the NRF with hand written responses from Doris Duke.
  - Correspondence regarding purchasing homes for preservation in Newport, R.I. Includes monthly expenses from Falcon Lair and Rough Point. 1968–1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes. 1968, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Statements of Receipts and Disbursements for NRF. Includes articles regarding a missing bust from the Julia Reed Rowe House. September 1968–December 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Statements of Receipts and Disbursements and Schedule of Properties Under Option. September 25, 1968–April 30, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings regarding NRF, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs (B & W) of moving historic home, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - “Report on Audit of Regulations Issued for Services Performed at ‘Prescott Farm,' For the Period October 1, 1968–August 30, 1969,” by Ford Property Improvements, Inc. October 10, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invoices for services rendered by Malcolm Vallance for appraising items donated to NRF by Doris Duke. 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Progress report for work performed at various NRF homes. July 18, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Report, The Prescott House, Portsmouth, R.I. October 23, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence relating to possible furniture purchases and other administrative tasks at the NRF. Includes copies of furniture appraisals and photos. 1971–1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries furniture catalogs, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Proposal to develop Queen Anne Square in Newport, R.I. and other records related to NRF, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to the purchase of homes for the NRF and some furnishings. 1973–1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to various NRF business activities, 1973-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Invoices and related materials for conservation work performed at NRF homes. 1974–1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Inventory of building materials, land and building summary, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence relating to daily administrative tasks at the NRF. 1976–1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Booklet, “The Newport Restoration Foundation, Prescott Farm, Whitehorne House, and 57 Restored Houses in Newport, R.I.” 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Memoranda regarding renting and renovating various NRF properties, including 51 Touro Street. Includes a Rental Agreement Contract. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 1 - Beds, benches, chests, and clocks, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 1 - Beds, benches, chests, and clocks ,1977 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 2 - Chairs, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 2 - Chairs, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 3 - Country Store & correspondence, 1977, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 4 - Cupboards, desks, sideboards, and fireplace fixtures, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 4 - Cupboards, desks, sideboards, and fireplace fixtures, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 5 - Kitchen furnishings, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 6 - Lighting fixtures, miniature furniture, and mirrors, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 6 - Lighting fixtures, miniature furniture, and mirrors, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 7 - Miscellaneous, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 7 - Miscellaneous, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 8 - Porcelain, crystal, and glassware, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 9 - Prints, paintings, and maps, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 9 - Prints, paintings, and maps, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 10 - Rugs, silver and pewter, sofas, and weaving items, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 10 - Rugs, silver and pewter, sofas, and weaving items, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 11 - Tables, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photo Inventory Vol. 11 - Tables, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NRF Weekly Reports, 1978 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NRF Weekly Reports, 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and Lease relating to Martha Smith’s rental of 3 Division Street with the Newport Restoration Foundation. 1978–1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NRF Weekly Reports, 1979 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NRF Weekly Reports, 1979 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Progress Reports, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sample Lease Form - NRF, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda regarding upkeep of the houses owned by NRF. Includes inventories of some of the homes. 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NRF Weekly Reports, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Water Billing Chart, 1981 Aug 25 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photo Inventory - Country Store, 1982 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photo Inventory - Country Store, 1982 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Photo Inventory - Guard House, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Alphabetical Project Index, 1982 Jul 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Numerical Project Index, 1982 Jul 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Certificate of Insurance and related materials covering automobiles belonging to the NRF. 1989–1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NRF Weekly Reports, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NRF Weekly Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Letter from Ben Reed, NRF, to Caroline Kennedy Schlossberg and John F. Kennedy, Jr. offering their condolences at the passing of Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis. May 25–26, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - NRF Business Plan, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation Trip Report, 1997 Jun 27 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - NRF Grants, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - NRF Budget and Proposed Marketing Plan, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1968 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1968 (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Ford Property Improvements-services performed at Prescott Farms, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1969 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1969 (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Ford Property Improvements-Audit, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ford Property Improvements-general correspondence and payments to FPI, 1969 (1 of 3) (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ford Property Improvements-general correspondence and payments to FPI, 1969 (2 of 3) (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Ford Property Improvements-inventory, 1969 Jul-Aug (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Ford Property Improvements-outside services, 1969 Oct (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Ford Property Improvements-outside services, 1969 Nov (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Ford Property Improvements-services performed at Rough Point, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - NRF labor analysis and administrative charges, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation work papers, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1970-1973 (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1970-1973 (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Pending legal action initiated by/against the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1970-1973 (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Pending legal action initiated by/against the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1970-1973 (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Draft of Mail. Includes financial information, 1972-1974 (1 of 6) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Draft of Mail. Includes financial information, 1972-1974 (2 of 6) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Draft of Mail. Includes financial information, 1972-1974 (3 of 6) (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Draft of Mail. Includes financial information, 1972-1974 (4 of 6) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Draft of Mail. Includes financial information, 1972-1974 (5 of 6) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Draft of Mail. Includes financial information, 1972-1974 (6 of 6) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding appraisal of five Oriental rugs, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence regarding employee performance appraisals, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1973 (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1973 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Photograph inventory of furniture and pedestals. Includes appraisals, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Photograph inventory of museum, ticket office, and executive offices. Includes appraisals and correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1974 (1 of 3) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1974 (2 of 3) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1974 (3 of 3) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1974 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1974 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Photograph inventory-miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Photograph inventory-State House Rhode Island, 19th Century Oak Furniture. Includes appraisal, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1975 (1 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1975 (2 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1975 (3 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation donations from the Doris Duke Foundation, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1976 (1 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1976 (2 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1976 (3 of 3) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous materials related to the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1976-1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - NRF Brochure #1, 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Thank you notes from visitors to Newport, 1976, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - NRF Brochure #2, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1977 (1 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1977 (2 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1977 (3 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper articles regarding NRF Tenants Suit, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1978 (1 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1978 (2 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and reports regarding administrative and financial activities of the NRF, 1978 (3 of 3) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Photograph inventory-items with photos missing needed to complete inventory, circa 1970s (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Photograph inventory-inventory cards and negatives, circa 1970s (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Newport inventory cards, circa 1970s (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Newport inventory cards, circa 1970s (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Photograph inventory of museum, ticket office, and executive offices. Includes appraisals and correspondence, circa 1970s (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Pete Wilczek-inventory cards of missing items at Rough Point, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Video cassette tape of the Samuel Whitehorne House. Includes memoranda regarding the videotape, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation Financial Statements, 1988 Jun 30 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation work progress report, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Brochures, NRF and Rough Point, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and weekly reports documenting the progress of the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1976-1980 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and weekly reports documenting the progress of the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1976-1980 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Map and streets of Newport Rhode Island, 1957 Aug (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Bound report "Archaelogical Investigations in Queen Anne Square Newport, Rhode Island", 1979 Jan (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda, correspondence, and work reports related to the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1970-1971, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Financial Records, 1968-1983
  Materials included in this series are NRF vouchers (categorized alphabetically), cost accounting statements, museum sales slips, summary cash statements, financial statements, and several ledgers containing cash, receipts and disbursements for the Newport Restoration Foundation.
  - Ford Property Improvement, Inc. Cost Accounting, 1968-1969, 1972 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ford Property Improvement, Inc. Cost Accounting, 1968-1969, 1972 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ford Property Improvement, Inc. Cost Accounting, 1968-1969, 1972 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - NRF Vouchers - "B", 1968-1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1968-1972 (Box 7)
  - NRF Vouchers - "A", 1969-1986 (1 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NRF Vouchers - "A", 1969-1986 (2 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NRF Vouchers - "A", 1969-1986 (3 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NRF Vouchers - "C", 1969-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NRF Vouchers - "D", 1969-1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NRF Vouchers - "F", 1969-1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NRF Vouchers - "H", 1969-1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NRF Vouchers - "I", 1969-1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NRF Vouchers - "K", 1969-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NRF Vouchers - "L", 1969-1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NRF Vouchers - "N", 1969-1986 (Box 1 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - NRF Vouchers - "N", 1969-1986 (Box 2 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NRF Vouchers - "N", 1969-1986 (Box 3 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NRF Vouchers - "N", 1969-1986 (Box 4 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NRF Vouchers - "N", 1969-1986 (Box 5 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - NRF Vouchers - "O", 1969-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NRF Vouchers - "R", 1969-1985 (1 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NRF Vouchers - "R", 1969-1985 (2 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NRF Vouchers - "R", 1969-1985 (3 of 5) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - NRF Vouchers - "R", 1969-1985 (4 of 5) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - NRF Vouchers - "R", 1969-1985 (5 of 5) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - NRF Vouchers - "S", 1969-1986 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - NRF Vouchers - "S", 1969-1986 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - NRF Vouchers - "U" and "V", 1969-1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - NRF Vouchers - "G", 1970-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - NRF Vouchers - "J", 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - NRF Vouchers - "T", 1970-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - NRF Vouchers - "E", 1971-1985 (1 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - NRF Vouchers - "E", 1971-1985 (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NRF Vouchers - "E", 1971-1985 (3 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NRF Vouchers - "M", 1971-1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NRF Vouchers - "W" and "Y", 1971-1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - J.T. O'Connell Cash and Carry Charges, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Payroll Distribution, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1973 Oct (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1973 Oct (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1973 Nov (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1973 Nov (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, 1973 Dec (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1973 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1973 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - J.T. O'Connell Cash and Carry Charges, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Payroll Distribution, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Jan (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Jan (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Feb (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Feb (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Mar (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Mar (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Apr (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Apr (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 May (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 May (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1974 Jun (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Jun (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Jun (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Jul (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Jul (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Aug (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 4)